Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
Is it about the cousins?
Are you sure Alys is happy with you?
What do I have to do
to prove that I love you?
And you're the only one I love!
Marry me.
Would you like to know
how she looks at me
even when she's mad at me?
The wedding is in two days.
Marry me,
or lose me forever.
Motherfucker!
- You asshole!
- Alys still loves me.
I can still feel it, Tripp.
Alys, we were both hurt.
Just this once.
Show him that I’m your priority.
It's so good.
Alys, that's enough!
Look at yourself, you're drunk!
- Then just leave if you want to!
- Alys, we have to go!
I have an important client
breakfast meeting tomorrow.
So, just leave me already!
Just like how your cousin left me.
I knew it.
That's what this is about.
Huh?
What?
Nothing.
Come on.
Let's go.
That's enough.
Just one more round, please!
Alys, I have a meeting tomorrow!
You're such a buzzkill!
Just like your cousin in highschool!
Hey!
Where are you going?
Didn't you say we were leaving?
I'm going to the restroom.
Meet me outside.
Are you sure you can?
Yes, I—
Hey, hey!
I said, I can manage!
Have you ordered already, Ma’am?
You can choose from our menu here.
Here you go.
Josh, please take their orders.
Alys!
Alys—
I’m sorry, ma’am, sorry!
Alys!
- Erica.
- Yes, Ma’am?
How are we on the deliveries?
Yes, Ma'am. They've arrived.
- Thank you. Please do an inventory check.
- Yes, Ma’am.
Alys! Alys!
Tofer, what?!
So early in the morning!
Did you hear?
Did you hear?!
I'm not deaf you
don't have to shout!
Did you hear already?
I'm not deaf, okay!
Would you stop
repeating yourself?
I can understand
you just fine!
And why are you so excited?
Does Riri have a concert
here in the Philippines?
Hey, I would love that!
But, I've got better news!
What is it?
Tripp's back!
Alys?
Earth to Alys!
Didn't you hear me?
Tripp is back!
Come on, move!
Huh?
Hey, Alys!
Calm down, calm down!
Inhale.
Exhale.
One more, one more.
Inhale.
Exhale.
Smells like lunch.
Just kidding.
So?
What?
Are you good now?
Okay.
Listen carefully.
I just came from there, right?
Then out of nowhere,
he showed up!
So, what?
Do you understand?
Apparently not.
But,
what I mean is
you should go see him, now!
Come on, come on!
I want to see him, but...
I'm scared.
What will I say to him?
Hi? Hello? How's New York?
Damn.
For the first time, I didn't
know what to say to Tripp.
Gosh.
Tripp's even more handsome now.
Watch out!
Hey!
Why are you still frozen?
Move, Perez!
Aren't you going to see him?
Maybe tomorrow.
Huh?
But why?
You've waited for him for so long.
And now he’s here!
These things take time, Tofer.
And we'll talk to
each other soon, okay?
Just let me do things the
way I want to do them.
I want to take my time.
Okay, fine.
Whatever you say.
Oh, wait.
Where were you the other night?
You know,
I waited for you outside.
When I came back for you,
you were gone!
I looked for you everywhere.
Even in the ladies' room!
What happened to you?
Drake!
What an asshole!
Is this guy for real?!
Wake up!
Wake up, Drake!
Who's Fier?
What's so funny about what I said?
Nothing.
Why are you here, Alys?
I asked you first.
Goodbye, Alys.
Drake!
Let go.
Let go, Alys!
Come on, Drake.
Tripp.
You left me for Tripp.
Now, go to him, Alys.
Stop bothering me.
Drake, what the fuck is your deal?!
Alys, what do you mean,
what's my deal?!
Who's Fier?
Did you replace me with her?!
You're drunk.
Go home.
Damn you, Palma!
Drake!
Damn it, Drake!
Stop it, Alys.
Alys.
Don't be jealous.
I'm sure you know that
I still love you, right?
When I told you that
I love you to the moon and back,
I meant that I'll never love
anyone else after you.
Our love was a great deal.
You've drained every bit of my love.
But that's it.
We had our time.
I'll still love you.
But leave me be.
Don't worry about Fier.
She's nothing compared to you.
I’m setting you free.
So, please let me go as well.
We should let go of each other.
Take care of my cousin.
Best wishes.
[in French] Only you.
Alys!
Come on,
I've been trying to talk to you!
Didn’t you hear what I said?
Is something bothering you?
What's in your head?
- I don't know how—
- Nothing.
Nothing.
Nothing, Tofer.
It's nothing.
- Let's go to Tripp?
- Huh?
Yes.
Let's go to Tripp.
Wow, what happened to
let me do things when
I wanna do them?
I wanna take my time.
Hmm?
You're serious about this.
So? Should we go to Tripp?
Great, I'll drive! Let's go, let's go!
Lani,
is Tripp home?
He's right outside.
Okay, thank you.
This calls for a drink!
Hang on.
I’ll grab some glasses!
Woo!
Let's party!
Your hair looks awful.
You're so annoying!
- I'm kidding!
- You're so mean to me!
Pretty?
Who’s that?
Says who?
They’re probably blind.
- Whatever!
- Hmm?
They probably needed money.
Hey!
Probably had bad eyesight.
They were only saying that
so you'd lend them money.
Alys!
Kei?
Come!
Join us.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Yes!
I'm good.
I’m okay.
Huh? Why are they together?
I thought they weren't on good terms.
Back in New York,
they never spoke to each other
because he thought Kei was a snob.
And Kei never liked
hanging out with him.
What happened?
Was there an apocalypse
and I wasn't informed?
What brings you here?
Um, I just finished my
internship for my MBA.
And I just wanted to visit
the Philippines.
You know, since I left after highschool,
I haven't been back.
What did your mom say?
I don't know.
Let them think what they want.
I'm an adult so,
I can do what I want with my life.
Technically, she's right about that.
But that's not the
answer I was looking for.
I mean...
Why is she here?
As in... here.
At Tripp's home.
With Tripp.
Oh! Speaking of Mom!
She wanted me to give you something.
Wait, it's in the car.
So...
You're back.
Yeah.
Why are you with Kei?
What the hell, Tripp?
What do you mean, what the hell?
You're avoiding me!
That's just in your head, Alys.
See?
You're calling me Alys.
I know something's wrong, Tripp.
That's your name, isn't it?
What's wrong about that?
Tripp!
You're so loud.
Keep it down.
You're still angry with me.
You're overthinking it.
Then talk to me!
For god's sake, talk to me
so I don't overthink.
Because you keep on avoiding me!
Just leave, Alys.
We're just going to fight.
Then let's fight.
Fight me! Do anything!
Just talk to me!
Go home!
Tripp, don't do this to me, please.
- Tripp.
- You said I’m not doing anything, right?
Exactly, you're not doing anything.
Please do something.
Please do something! Anything!
Anything!
This hurts me more than fighting.
Please, don't.
Then give me space, Alys.
We'll talk when I'm better, okay?
What about me?
What if I'm not okay?
Did you consider how I might feel?
How about me?
Did you think about me?
You never did.
I chose you.
I chose you, Tripp.
I chose you!
But here you are acting
such a fucking asshole.
You chose me?
Me? You chose me?
You never chose me!
I was nothing but an option.
Because Drake left you.
So how about Tripp instead.
That's how it was, right?
Ahh...
I’ll just choose Tripp.
He's the one who's around.
He's close.
Did you think that
would make me happy?
It fucked me up, Alys.
It fucked me up real bad.
Let's party!
- Let's go!
- Hee hee!
Come on! Let's get drunk!
Come on, let's go!
Why are you crying?
Is it Drake again?
I swear, if I see him again—
Alys.
It's gonna be okay.
Did Tripp argue with you again?
What?
Why Tripp?
He's her boyfriend, right?
Why would he make her cry?
No more questions for now.
Alys...
Alys, calm down.
Calm down.
- Alys, Alys...
- It’s okay, Alys.
Calm down, stop crying.
Stop crying.
Alys!
Honey, are you ready?
I know you're not in
your best mood right now.
But maybe this party can
take your mind off things.
Alright?
Cheer up!
You're wasting your beauty!
Okay?
Alright, I'll be downstairs.
Don't take too long.
Okay, Mommy. I'll be right down.
Okay!
At least my family's okay.
Even if everything else is broken.
It's okay, Alys.
You're okay.
Alys, let's go!
Coming!
Hon, remember about the
eye care foundation?
You know what?
Susan donated like 500,000.
We probably should donate.
- What do you think?
- I don’t feel like going.
We'll talk about it later.
So, kids?
Enjoy yourselves, okay?
Go ahead, alright?
Oh, hi, Mr. Lim!
I'm glad you decided
to get out of the house.
It has been days.
You know what, Dane?
If it wasn't required to bring your
family I wouldn't have attended.
Well, we're here.
Let's just make the most out of it.
Hey, where are you going, Dane?
- I'm leaving.
- You're leaving me too?
Such a weirdo.
Suck it up, Alys.
You can do this. Let's go.
Dane, wait up!
Where is he?
Oh my god, I'm so—
I'm sorry.
Alys! You little witch!
Let's go, Fier.
I hate you, you know.
Let's go.
You broke up with him,
but I still can't get him from you.
I'm sorry, Alys. She's just drunk.
You... horrible person.
Horrible person!
Enough!
No!
You don't understand!
Even though you're a horrible person,
I can't get him from you!
Let's go, Fier.
I'm not done with you yet!
You are a horrible person!
You're a witch! You're horrible!
Horrible!
Horrible is a bit much.
They said it was a
miracle that I survived.
Thanks to all the saints
my mom cursed at,
and to the healing potion she
got all the way from Siquijor.
- Alys!
- Hmm?
Aren't you supposed to be
at your work today?
They can manage by themselves.
They're grown ups.
Alys.
That's your business
we're talking about.
That cupcake shop is
your baby, remember?
I know!
They'll manage.
- Dear God.
- Relax.
That's it!
This is getting out of hand.
Enough with the sulking!
Mom, I—
You know what?
You've locked yourself in this
house since the office party.
You need to get out of the house!
You know what?
You're going with us later.
That's not gonna work.
I've had enough of
your sighs and silence.
And you're going.
Where?
A fundraiser event.
Oh come on, Mom.
God, Alys!
Even if you throw a fit,
you're going with us, okay?
Mom!
You're going!
Mommy!
No!
Please stop with bringing
me to your work functions!
Have mercy!
Not working, Alys, okay?
So pick up a nice dress.
I'll have Nanny pick you up, okay?
Alright, see you later!
Mom!
Not even a message.
Nothing from him on social media!
Well, he did ask for space, right?
Yeah, right.
We're just on a break,
not done.
Whatever you guys say.
Wait,
is Tripp doing photography again?
Back in New York, he kept
pushing me to be his model.
Aya?
I need you!
Hang on, Bestie.
Your mom just came in.
I need to present our
designs for our client.
I don't want to get yelled at again.
Okay, good luck.
I told you working there is a bad idea.
My mom is such a terror boss.
- At least, I'm learning.
- Aya!
Yes, Auntie! Coming!
- Bye, Bestie. Have to go.
- Okay, bestie. Bye!
Is this Kei?!
No way.
She'd never betray me.
Kei's the closest thing I
have to a sister, next to Aya.
No...
No, she'll never hurt me.
Mommy's right.
I've been wallowing in self-pity,
that I forgot how to live.
There's more to life
than this mess I'm in.
I need to see that my life
is actually still worth living.
That the people around me
are still worth trusting.
I need to breathe. Breathe, Alys.
Get yourself ready.
Mommy!
Are you there in the venue?
Yes, Honey.
Okay, I'm also here in the lobby.
I'll see you there.
Alright, see you!
Okay, bye!
Where you at?
Fundraising event?
Are you gonna be there?
Kei isn't doing anything wrong,
Yet...
something within me makes
me start to hate her.
It's the worst feeling in the world
when you start to doubt
your own bestfriend.
I need a resolve.
It can't always be like this.
Yeah! See you!
See you, Kei.
And talk to you, as well.
I can't keep living like this.
All this paranoia,
will be the death of me.
You know what?
Just enjoy the night.
I'll try, Dad.
But I don't even know where—
- Mr. Guzman
- It’s gonna be fun.
Mr. Montreal!
How are you?
I'm good.
Meet my daughter, Alys.
Hi, Alys.
Oh, nice to meet you, sir.
Alys, you remember Mr. Montreal, right?
One of our business partners.
Yes, I do, Dad.
By the way,
I want you to meet my daughter.
This is Natalia.
Hi, Natalia!
Sorry, she's a bit shy.
So, Alys...
you good on your own?
Yes, Dad. I'll manage.
Alright.
Hi, Natalia!
- Nice seeing you.
Is Kei here?
Thank god!
Someone I actually know.
What happened to you?
Wow, someone’s thirsty.
Goodness, thank God you're here!
Mommy couldn't make it so
I was sent here to be her proxy.
Are you with your family?
What about you?
Did you come alone?
It was a short notice.
I'm glad you're here.
How did I ever doubt her?
I know she'll never hurt me.
I need more wine!
Looks like it.
Let's go.
- Whatever, Alys.
- About to start singing?
- Hey!
- I'm kidding.
Hello, ladies!
- Hi, Uncle!
- Hi, Kei.
Nice to see you.
Dear...
you can only spend up
to one million tonight, okay?
Okay, Dad!
As if I plan on bidding tonight.
I'm just saying!
So I'll just go to the front, okay?
Go ahead, Dad.
You guys enjoy yourselves.
Thank you, Dad.
So...
have you seen Tripp?
Did you two fight?
I saw him recently.
You guys should talk it out.
Like it or not...
the problem won't go away
unless you two talk about it.
You're just dragging it out.
I really want to talk to him.
I'm just waiting for him.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for your patience.
Kindly settle down and take your seats.
Cut the self-pity, Perez!
You know Tripp followed
you around like a dog once.
You're worth it, okay?
Never forget that.
I really missed you, Kei.
I missed you, too.
All of our proceeds from tonight’s program
will go directly to DAHON.
A Dedicated Alliance for
Helping and Healing Our Nature.
Let's give it up for DAHON, everybody.
Up for grabs first,
is a 90-year old bottle of wine courtesy
of the very generous Sandoval family.
Made by the best wine
makers in all of France.
My god, Alys.
Ever since we were in New York,
when it comes to love,
you never failed to be stupid.
Ouch!
Isn't stupid a bit much?
Can't I just be someone
who gives it my all?
And...
a hopeless romantic.
- A little?
- Just a little bit.
A little that's also kind of a lot.
Wow!
Whatever, Alys.
Let’s stick with that.
Oh!
Hang on, it's Mommy.
I need to take this.
You may now start the
bidding at 100,000 pesos.
Anybody have a 100,000?
Anybody interested?
Yes, Mr. Santos how about
we bump it to a 115,000 pesos?
Yes, Mrs. Alivar! 115,000?
To the gentleman
in the black tie. 115,000!
How about we
bump it to 120,000?
Where is Kei?
Did she forget to
come back for me?
Gosh, everyone seems to do so.
Where did she go?
Mrs. Alivar, sold!
For 200,000 pesos!
And now, for our next auction item.
An original painting by
Alejandro Perin.
The bidding starts at 250,000.
Thank you, Ma’am!
Do I hear 300,000?
It's like I'm talking to the
slowest person in the world!
You weren't answering my calls!
What was I gonna do?
My god, Tripp!
We can't be together!
There is no us!
Are you dumb? Are you insane?
Maybe both!
Kei, don’t do—
Get it together, Tripp!
You're still with Alys! My best friend!
How many times do
I have to repeat that?
My god!
You're giving me a headache!
I don't care about you,
Tripp Marco Palma!
Dating my friend's ex, is not
something I'm comfortable with!
Not now,
not ever!
So please, stop this already!
You have to fix things with Alys!
She's a good person.
You should be grateful she stuck by you!
If it were me,
I'd have left you a long time ago!
So, leave.
Before she sees us.
Never do this again, okay?
Please!
I'm going home. Sorry for ditching.
Rain check?
Calm down, Alys.
Everything will make sense in time.
You're okay.
Tripp...
Can we talk?
I know you heard
Kei and I talking, Alys.
What are you, a masochist?
Tripp...
I thought we were just taking a break?
We never broke up, right?
Okay, Alys.
Let's break up.
Are you being serious, Tripp?
I refuse, Tripp.
I will not let you.
You’re not leaving me.
You're not leaving me, Tripp!
Listen.
There's nothing left.
I'm done.
Let's end this.
I'm tired.
You're just saying that!
You're not even trying!
Do you even hear yourself, Alys?
All these years, Alys.
The only thing I've done is try.
Do you know where we went wrong?
It's how you acknowledge me.
Even for just one day.
One day is all I ask,
that you get to acknowledge
and see my efforts,
but it just never happened.
You never saw it.
I'm done, Zy.
So, please...
stop being selfish.
All I want
is a life without you.
A life that isn't focused around you.
That's all I want.
Please let me live my life.
Don't you love me anymore?
I still do.
Then why are you hurting me?
Because you never loved me
the way I wanted you to, Perez.
All of my life,
I had to share with Drake.
You know that.
That's why, when it comes to women,
I don’t want to have to share too.
But I chose you.
No, you didn't, Alys.
You never did.
It was Drake.
- It always has been.
- That’s not true.
That’s not true.
It was Drake
and it always will be.
I've accepted that, Alys.
Come on, Tripp.
Tripp...
Don't worry.
I promise you,
go after Drake first.
And if it doesn’t work out,
I'll come running back to you.
Why do you have to be such a jerk?
You and I both know
what'll happen if I won’t be.
I'm just gonna crawl
myself back to you.
I'm pathetic without you, Perez.
Then, let's be pathetic together.
You know how happy
I am when I'm with you.
Tripp, please. Don't leave me.
Tripp, please don't leave me.
Please, don't leave me.
Don't leave me, Tripp.
- Perez, Perez!
- Don't leave me.
What we need to try,
is to end things for real.
Don't worry.
I promise you my name.
If Drake doesn't come back to you,
then I'll marry you.
But for now...
that's enough, Zy.
Don't leave me.
This is hard for me, too.
You're my soulmate.
Sometimes soulmates
don't end up with each other.
I'm sorry, Zy.
Tripp, please don't leave me.
Friends?
You'll marry me someday, Tripp.
You'll marry me.
I am not even sure anymore.
Tripp, no!
I'm setting you free.
So, please let me go as well.
We should let go of each other.
Take care of my cousin.
Best wishes.
[in French] Only you.
I'm sorry, Alys.
I have to do this.
I love you.
I guess I love you more
than I ever did.
And I know what I did hurt you.
But if I stay, I'll only confuse you.
I want to reach out to you.
I want to hold you close
and tell you that I want us back.
But you already turned me down
when you didn't show up for our wedding.
That broke my heart, Alys.
Nothing hurts more than not being
chosen by the person you love so deeply.
If we're really meant to be,
I know we'll always find
our way back to each other.
Thank you for everything, my Noob.
I'll wait for you until the very end.
Since the day I met you, Alys,
I did nothing but love you with all I had.
I never ran out of love to give.
Even when I knew deep down,
that I'd always come second.
But now?
It hurts.
It hurts me, Alys.
It hurts me so much.
I love you so much.
That’s why...
I'm setting you free.
This may destroy me but...
I'll do this
because I love you.
I love you, Alys.
I always will.
On the next episode of
Dating Alys Perez.
Auntie said you’re taking a vacation.
Yes, I’m on the way
to Batangas.
Drake?!
Actually Ma'am,
all rooms are occupied.
But the good thing is...
the upper villa is still
available for the two of you!
Enjoy your stay!
Love, love, love!
This place is a perfect place
to relax, enjoy, and be in love.
With the nature, of course.
What the?!
Isn't the sunset so beautiful?
As beautiful as you.